Guide to the
Brown University Library
- MNGW_chapter 9_KB Pass 7x9.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/~Pages for MNGW/Chapter 9/Date created: 2012-06-21 18:42:37 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-07-05 17:46:58 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- MNGW Chapter 6.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/~Pages for MNGW/Chapter 6 SEX SEX SEX SEX SEX SEX SEX/Date created: 2012-03-16 11:13:14 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-05-17 14:58:51 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 8 MNGW_chapter 8_KB Pass 7x9.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/MNGW Final Draft KB->Routledge/Chapters—Apple Pages/Date created: 2012-06-21 13:05:48 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-07-15 12:18:59 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Guidepost & Control System Charts.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/Touring/Workshop Handouts/Role Play Workshop/Date created: 2009-03-18 10:48:52 EDT-0400Date modified: 2009-03-18 12:31:45 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- MNGW Chapter 2.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My Gender Workbook/Chapter Drafts in Pages format/Date created: 2012-02-06 14:55:31 EST-0500Date modified: 2012-02-09 13:44:53 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Tao of Mitzvah Etc for Neherim.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/Trans For the Fun of It/Mine Me for Transition Pieces/Tao of Sabbath Mitvah Boddhisatva ƒ/Date created: 2011-10-28 12:10:20 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-10-28 13:37:06 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Repair Return Note Etymotic 2.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Receipts/Date created: 2009-03-10 12:19:34 EDT-0400Date modified: 2009-03-11 21:00:41 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 316 HouseSit Notes Apr2013 KB.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/Where's My Home/Old House Docs/Date created: 2013-04-26 15:51:27 EDT-0400Date modified: 2013-04-27 10:34:32 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- KB-Acting-Wkshop-Handout-2.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/Touring/Workshop Handouts/Acting Workshop/Date created: 2010-10-22 14:34:28 EDT-0400Date modified: 2010-10-22 14:40:58 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- HCW_Text_KBpass.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/HCW iPhone App/Date created: 2010-04-25 12:32:36 EDT-0400Date modified: 2010-04-25 16:21:14 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Kate Bornstein, Book Release Event-May 1st, 120406.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Dixon Place Launch/Date created: 2012-04-30 12:23:44 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-04-30 13:20:47 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 316 HouseSit Notes 10:13.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/Where's My Home/Old House Docs/Date created: 2013-10-12 18:43:11 EDT-0400Date modified: 2013-10-12 18:43:11 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- kb meds sheet 09.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Dropbox/kb-health-dropbox/Date created: 2009-06-05 12:37:44 EDT-0400Date modified: 2009-06-07 16:02:24 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Gender Is A Wooly Worm 1st Draft 09.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/Gender Outlaw 2nd ed/GO 2nd Ed Attic/Date created: 2016-05-05 10:42:24 EDT-0400Date modified: 2016-05-05 10:42:24 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 101 working table.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/~Pages for MNGW/Chapter 5 There's Only One Gender—Yours/Date created: 2012-07-02 14:40:45 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-07-03 15:16:08 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Blurb Letter Samuel Delany copy.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/~Memoir PR/Blurber Letters/Date created: 2011-09-27 19:03:03 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-09-28 13:23:42 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Gender Outlaw by Kate Bornstein and S. Bear Bergman.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/Gender Outlaw Next Gen/Date created: 2009-05-11 13:12:03 EDT-0400Date modified: 2009-05-11 13:12:03 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Tku Lambda Lit Trans.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/Completed Articles & Talks/Lambda Lit 2011/Date created: 2011-05-26 13:00:00 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-05-26 13:02:18 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- cheap sex with bc 3.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/BC this and that/Date created: 2009-02-02 18:24:57 EST-0500Date modified: 2009-02-02 18:30:24 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- A Queer And Pleasant Danger Pre Copy Edit.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Just Before Copy Edits/For epub/Date created: 2011-09-13 22:08:54 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-09-13 22:51:07 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- My Old Gender Workbook MASTER.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/Old Workbook Files/Date created: 2012-01-03 14:29:19 EST-0500Date modified: 2012-01-03 14:30:58 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- queer and pleasant danger book 2 clean.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Attic Queer & Pleasant/Edits Back & Forth/Cleanest, Newest/e-pub format/Date created: 2011-08-24 15:07:20 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-09-04 11:55:33 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- House-Sitter Factoids.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/Touring/House Sitting/Date created: 2008-01-19 11:42:53 EST-0500Date modified: 2009-03-10 11:23:28 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- kb meds sheet 09-3.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Dropbox/kb-health-dropbox/kb-health to 2012/Date created: 2010-01-13 10:45:12 EST-0500Date modified: 2010-01-13 21:15:52 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 02 Solving the Gender Puzzle.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/Workbook Attic/My New Gender Workbook Working by Chapter/Date created: 2012-01-03 14:51:54 EST-0500Date modified: 2012-01-03 14:52:42 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- apology to neighbors.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/Correspondence, Blurbs, & Referrals/Date created: 2012-12-02 13:09:45 EST-0500Date modified: 2012-12-02 13:35:23 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- queer and pleasant danger book 1 KB pass 2.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Attic Queer & Pleasant/Edits Back & Forth/Now With Beacon/Book 1/Date created: 2011-07-29 11:02:30 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-08-12 14:16:15 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- KATE BORNSTEIN TOUR.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Library/Mail/V5/8D5A1E6A-3871-48CC-B85B-B014FE3DEA28/Tour Venues Booked.mbox/Been There, Done That.mbox/UK Tour Feb 2016.mbox/7FC563F4-99CD-45EC-AFCA-5A7ABA6D9DF2/Data/6/7/2/Attachments/276044/2.2/Date created: 2015-11-30 11:15:22 EST-0500Date modified: 2015-11-30 11:15:22 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Men Women Rest of Us Perf Notes 2012.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/Touring/y2kate & TTB/KB Touring Pieces folder/~~current/Date created: 2012-07-27 16:48:44 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-07-27 16:48:44 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- KB Meds Nov 2012 1.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Dropbox/kb-health-dropbox/KB Meds/Meds Nov 2012/Date created: 2012-11-26 13:38:05 EST-0500Date modified: 2012-11-27 17:38:34 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Bornstein Edit Salon 2-2.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/~Memoir PR/Salon Excerpt/Date created: 2012-05-03 12:06:57 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-05-03 12:15:40 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- KB_AuthorPublicity&Marketing.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Publicity/Date created: 2011-05-03 21:24:02 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-05-24 14:07:12 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Scientology New Yorker.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Scientology ƒ/Date created: 2011-02-21 12:09:18 EST-0500Date modified: 2011-02-21 12:09:18 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- My Old Gender Workbook Working Copy.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/Old Workbook Files/Date created: 2012-01-03 14:56:46 EST-0500Date modified: 2012-01-03 15:02:17 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 3-4 Minutes 4th Annual Womens Awards.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/Utah Pride QvS/Stonewall Democrats/Date created: 2010-01-21 14:34:58 EST-0500Date modified: 2010-02-05 14:42:06 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- MNGW chapter 7 Gold sketch.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/~Pages for MNGW/Chapter 7 Get Ready To Do Your Gender/Date created: 2012-07-04 19:55:05 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-07-04 19:55:39 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 3-3 Stages Of Life.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Library/Mail/V5/27F8CF84-27C9-45EB-BBC2-180B448CB245/Sent Messages.mbox/7FC563F4-99CD-45EC-AFCA-5A7ABA6D9DF2/Data/7/7/1/Attachments/177847/2/Date created: 2015-10-03 13:54:10 EDT-0400Date modified: 2015-10-03 13:54:10 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- BalladOfLittleJo_by_Kate_B.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/Itty Bitty Archive/Ballad of Little Jo for Out Dot Com/Date created: 2011-01-11 19:29:52 EST-0500Date modified: 2011-01-11 20:42:26 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- kb letter to the revolution for B.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/Articles-Talks In Progress/Letter to the Revolution/Date created: 2017-01-07 14:32:04 EST-0500Date modified: 2017-01-07 14:32:04 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- do u c p.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/Where's My Home/Old House Docs/Date created: 2013-07-21 16:58:07 EDT-0400Date modified: 2013-07-21 16:58:37 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- BILD Interview.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Edel Books PR/Date created: 2013-03-12 12:54:32 EDT-0400Date modified: 2013-03-12 14:50:10 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Femme Conf 2010 Keynote Reader-3.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/Trans For the Fun of It/Mine Me for Transition Pieces/Femme Conf Keynote/Date created: 2010-08-20 15:37:39 EDT-0400Date modified: 2010-08-20 19:33:28 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- New EAM for T&GNC People Chapter KB pass.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/In Others Words/Barbara Words/Date created: 2017-04-01 14:19:01 EDT-0400Date modified: 2017-04-01 14:19:01 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- MNGW Chapter 5 KB pass.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/~Pages for MNGW/Chapter 5 There's Only One Gender—Yours/Date created: 2012-05-27 11:03:21 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-07-06 12:27:33 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- kb meds sheet 09-3.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Dropbox/kb-health-dropbox/Date created: 2010-01-13 10:45:12 EST-0500Date modified: 2010-01-13 21:15:52 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Rafe Posey Recc to Brown Grad School.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/Correspondence, Blurbs, & Referrals/Date created: 2010-12-16 12:30:54 EST-0500Date modified: 2010-12-16 13:35:44 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Dear Galley Reader Letter.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Cleaned Desktop Files/Office/Date created: 2011-12-11 14:17:18 EST-0500Date modified: 2011-12-11 15:02:43 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Coming Out.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Dixon Place Launch/Readings for Dixon Place/Date created: 2012-04-29 18:09:18 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-04-29 18:09:18 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 3-1 I Meet Daddy Man to Man.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Attic Queer & Pleasant/~~ First Draft ~~/Date created: 2010-07-03 15:10:50 EDT-0400Date modified: 2010-07-03 15:30:53 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- letter to irs re payment agreement.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Dropbox/Kate Bornstein Financial/Older Finances/IRS Payment Agreement/Date created: 2011-02-17 14:22:06 EST-0500Date modified: 2011-02-17 14:35:25 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- measuring sexuality by.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/~Pages for MNGW/Chapter 6 SEX SEX SEX SEX SEX SEX SEX/Date created: 2012-03-29 11:00:49 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-03-31 02:11:49 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Blurb Letter Jenny Boylan.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/~Memoir PR/Blurber Letters/Date created: 2011-09-27 17:08:45 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-09-28 13:24:37 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- An Afternoon of Bridge.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Gender Complete/Fictionmania Downloads/Date created: 2010-11-26 20:08:52 EST-0500Date modified: 2010-11-26 21:02:33 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Treatment Ideas Post Lobectomy.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Dropbox/kb-health-dropbox/kb-health to 2012/Date created: 2012-11-09 23:04:02 EST-0500Date modified: 2012-11-09 23:04:02 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- what does mean mean.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/Itty Bitty Archive/What Does Mean Mean/Date created: 2010-10-24 20:05:38 EDT-0400Date modified: 2010-10-24 21:29:48 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 3-4 where it gets complicated 1st hackjob.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Attic Queer & Pleasant/3-4 OK This Is Where It Gets Complicated/3-4 Round One/Date created: 2011-06-05 12:08:42 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-06-09 14:35:30 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- MNGW_chapter 6_KB Pass 7x9.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/~Pages for MNGW/Chapter 6 SEX SEX SEX SEX SEX SEX SEX/Date created: 2012-06-20 12:38:18 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-07-04 18:11:31 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Kate Bornstein One Sheet.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/Touring/Newsletters/09-10 Newsletter Folder/Date created: 2009-08-20 21:42:43 EDT-0400Date modified: 2009-08-21 16:36:44 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- KB recc for Laura.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/Correspondence, Blurbs, & Referrals/Laura Antoniou Lambda/Date created: 2011-02-26 11:57:34 EST-0500Date modified: 2011-02-26 11:57:34 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- queer and pleasant danger book 1 KB pass 2 clean.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Attic Queer & Pleasant/Edits Back & Forth/Now With Beacon/Book 1/Date created: 2011-08-05 15:08:45 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-08-12 14:33:45 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 4 MNGW Chapter 4 Gold sketch.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/~Pages for MNGW/Chapter 4 Let Why = Why/Date created: 2012-07-14 17:00:58 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-07-14 17:03:11 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Epilogue-Hello Sweetie Raw.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Attic Queer & Pleasant/Epilogue/Date created: 2011-09-05 12:36:17 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-09-05 17:29:31 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- MNGW Chapter 5 Gold sketch.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/~Pages for MNGW/Chapter 5 There's Only One Gender—Yours/Date created: 2012-07-06 12:28:03 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-07-06 12:32:09 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Backup of Two Forms of ID.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Gender Complete/Fictionmania Downloads/Date created: 2010-11-26 17:52:21 EST-0500Date modified: 2010-11-26 18:26:00 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- KB_OpEd_Aug2014_Pages_09.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/Trans For the Fun of It/Mine Me for Transition Pieces/Op Ed Tipping Points and Trannies/Date created: 2014-08-26 14:12:27 EDT-0400Date modified: 2014-08-26 14:12:27 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- NUJLS Mitzvah Text.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/Trans For the Fun of It/Mine Me for Transition Pieces/Tao of Sabbath Mitvah Boddhisatva ƒ/Date created: 2009-04-04 23:19:45 EDT-0400Date modified: 2009-05-02 21:34:42 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 3-3 Stages Of Life.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Attic Queer & Pleasant/3-3 Under Construction/Date created: 2011-05-02 18:31:30 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-05-03 21:21:26 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- inherit the earth opening.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/Inherit The Earth/samples/Date created: 2009-07-08 23:31:18 EDT-0400Date modified: 2009-07-08 23:31:18 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Ecstasy Is Necessary Review KB 1st Draft.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/In Others Words/Barbara Words/BC Ecstasy Is Neccessary/Date created: 2012-02-28 12:35:13 EST-0500Date modified: 2012-02-28 15:27:04 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- New Introduction copy KB pass.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/In Others Words/Barbara Words/Date created: 2017-06-14 17:31:12 EDT-0400Date modified: 2017-06-14 17:31:12 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Hello Cruel Bullies ♀ History 2011.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/Touring/y2kate & TTB/KB Touring Pieces folder/~~current/Date created: 2011-03-22 09:52:06 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-03-23 04:44:50 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Epilogue-Hello Sweetie KB 1st Pass.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Attic Queer & Pleasant/Epilogue/Date created: 2011-09-05 17:31:06 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-09-05 17:31:06 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- KB_OpEd_Aug2014-2.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/Trans For the Fun of It/Mine Me for Transition Pieces/Op Ed Tipping Points and Trannies/Date created: 2014-08-26 16:01:12 EDT-0400Date modified: 2014-08-26 16:01:12 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 78C821AE-B13E-48CF-8D9C-135C6D40EA09.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Library/Autosave Information/03BC463D-81E4-4EF6-818D-F0795B084959.genstore.noindex/Date created: 2012-04-16 22:45:16 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-04-17 15:42:40 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- QueerAndPleasantProposal.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Date created: 2010-07-09 11:24:13 EDT-0400Date modified: 2010-07-09 13:53:51 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 3 KB Edit Chap 3.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/My New Gender Workbook - 1st Proofs for KB/Date created: 2013-01-15 22:08:24 EST-0500Date modified: 2013-01-15 23:19:17 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Lucia Miel 1st draft KB notes.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/Gender Outlaw Next Gen/Date created: 2010-02-07 15:17:40 EST-0500Date modified: 2010-02-07 22:18:17 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- MNGW Chapter 1_KBpass.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/~Pages for MNGW/Chapter 1 Gender Aptitude/Date created: 2012-05-15 11:51:57 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-07-01 15:12:24 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- JJ_Reading.pages